Herbert Waide Hemphill
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Material, 1776-1998, Series 7:; (Box 10-19, 28-29, OV 31; 9.5 linear feet)
  - Travel Booklets and Brochures (Box 15)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Galleries, 1996, undated (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Museums, 1950-1993, undated, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 64-65)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Organizations, 1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 66-67)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Conferences and Symposia, 1979-1996, undated (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Schools and Classes, 1973-1990, undated, (Oversized material also housed in OV 31) (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Lectures, 1990-1996, undated (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Antiques and Craft Shops, 1969-1996, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Films, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Books and Magazines, 1952-1997, undated, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 3-5)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Food and Restaurants, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Booklets and Brochures for Household Items and Audio-Visual Equipment, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Booklets and Brochures on Historical Topics, 1957-1969, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Autographed Booklet The Black Swan and Other Poems by James Merrill, 1946 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Autographed Booklet The Blood of Jesus by Thomas Jefferson Flanagan, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Brochures, 1953-1996, undated, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 11-13)
    - Miscellaneous Booklets, 1965-1985, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 14-16)
    - Theater Program, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Theater Programs, 1964-1996, (42 folders) (Box 16, Folder 18-60)
    - Ballet Programs, 1966, 1969, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 61-62)
    - Opera Programs, 1962-1967, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 63-65)
    - Cinema Programs, 1965-1969, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 66-67)
    - James Smithson Society Programs, 1987-1996, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 68-70)
    - Smithsonian Benefactors' Circle Programs, 1992-1995, undated (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous Programs, 1896-1997, undated, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 72-74)
    - Miscellaneous Tickets, 1935-1992, undated (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Souvenir Menus, 1966-1995, undated (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Picture Postcards, Places (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Alabama, undated (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Arkansas; Arizona, undated (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - California, 1927, undated (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Colorado; Connecticut, undated (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Delaware, undated (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - District of Columbia; Florida, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Georgia, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Hawaii, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Illinois; Indiana, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Iowa; Kentucky, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Louisiana, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Maine, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Maryland, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts, undated, (3 folders) (Box 17, Folder 10-12)
    - Michigan; Minnesota, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Mississippi; Montana, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - New Hampshire, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - New Jersey; New Mexico, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - New York, undated, (5 folders) (Box 17, Folder 17-21)
    - North Carolina, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
    - Ohio, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania, undated, (4 folders) (Box 17, Folder 25-28)
    - Rhode Island, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - South Carolina, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
    - South Dakota; Tennessee, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Texas, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Vermont, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 34-35)
    - Virginia, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Washington State; Wisconsin, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Africa (Ivory Coast; Mali), undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Argentina, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Austria (Salzburg; Vienna), undated, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 40-41)
    - Bermuda, undated (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Borneo; Brazil, undated (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Canada, undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Ceylon, undated (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - China; Hong Kong; Macau, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17, Folder 46-47)
    - Crete, undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Cuba, undated (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Dominican Republic, undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Egypt, undated (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - England; Scotland; Wales, undated, (3 folders) (Box 17, Folder 52-54)
    - France, undated, (3 folders) (Box 17, Folder 55-57)
    - Germany, undated, (5 folders) (Box 17, Folder 58-62)
    - Greece, undated, (4 folders) (Box 17, Folder 63-66)
    - Haiti; India, undated (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Italy, undated, (6 folders) (Box 17, Folder 68-73)
    - Jamaica, undated (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Japan, undated, (7 folders) (Box 17, Folder 75-81)
    - Japan, undated, (9 folders) (Box 18, Folder 1-9)
    - Korea; Lebanon, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Liechtenstein; Malaysia (Singapore), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Mallorca, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Mexico, undated, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 13-14)
    - Panama; Peru, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Poland, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Portugal, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Puerto Rico, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Russia, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Tibet; Trinidad, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Turkey; Uruguay; Vietnam, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Virgin Islands, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Yugoslavia, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Picture Postcards, Art Work (Box 18)
    - Adams - Archuletta, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Giuseppe Arcimboldo, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Barnes - Black, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - William Blake, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Bonnard - Butterworth, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Casimir - Cassatt, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Paul Cezanne, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Chagall - Cranach, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - H. H. Cross, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Crowell - Cruise, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Dali - DeChirico, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Edgar Degas, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Dekker - Dürer, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Earl - Gallegos, undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Paul Gauguin, undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Goya - Guy, undated (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Hanson - Hunt, undated (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Dudley Huppler, undated, (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 41-42)
    - Ingres - Johnson, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Kaay - Kuiper, undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Laurencin - Licinio, undated (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Manet - Matteson, undated (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Henri Matisse, undated (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - McCarthy - Modigliani, undated (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Claude Monet, undated (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Moore - Mundi, undated (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Nast - Osgood, undated (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Palanquet - Phillips, undated (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Pablo Picasso, undated (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Pickett - Rembrandt, undated (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Auguste Renoir, undated (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Ricker - Rousseau, undated (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Schiele - Skyllas, undated (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Smith - Sutherland, undated (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Taber - Turner, undated (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Utrillo - Van Dok, undated (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Vincent Van Gogh, undated (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Van Leyden - Von Egloffstein, undated (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Wall - Wheeler, undated (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Whistler - Wood, undated (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Yoakum - Zorach, undated (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Unidentified Artists (arranged by country) 1940, undated, (27 folders) (Box 18, Folder 66-92)
    - Unidentified Artists (arranged by country), 1940, undated, (18 folders) (Box 19, Folder 1-18)
  - Novelty Picture Postcards, undated, (11 folders) (Box 19, Folder 19-29)
  - Miscellaneous Reproductions of Art Work, 1991, undated, (2 folders; Oversized material also housed in Box 29) (Box 19, Folder 30-31)
  - Sheet Music by Charles Trenet, 1945-1947 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Postage Stamps, 1992, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Business Cards for Hemphill, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Business Cards for Artists, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Business Cards for Others (arranged by trade), undated, (10 folders) (Box 19, Folder 36-45)
  - Miscellaneous Stationery, undated, (5 folders) (Box 19, Folder 46-50)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1776-1994, undated, (4 folders) (Box 19, Folder 51-54)
  - Five Oversized Clippings, undated, (from Box 10, Folder 16) (Box 28)
  - Oversized Clipping, 1969, (from Box 10, Folder 42) (Box 28)
  - Three Oversized Clippings, 1976, (from Box 10, Folders 53, 56, 57) (Box 28)
  - Oversized Clipping, 1991, (from Box 11, Folder 41) (Box 28)
  - Oversized Exhibition Announcement for Andy Warhol, undated, (from Box 11, Folder 64) (Box 29)
  - Oversized Catalog for Exhibition in Japan, 1957, (from Box 12, Folder 10) (Box 29)
  - Oversized Exhibition Announcement in Velvet Bag for The Orange Show, 1997, (from Box 14, Folder 36) (Box 29)
  - Oversized Calendar of Events, 1992, (from Box 14, Folder 65) (Box 29)
  - Oversized Brochure about Miles Carpenter, undated, (from Box 15, Folder 2) (Box 29)
  - Oversized Booklet about Travel in Japan, undated, (from Box 15, Folder 30) (Box 29)
  - Oversized Brochure for Lithograhs by Savelli, 1962, (from Box 15, Folder 61) (Box 29)
  - Four Oversized Miscellaneous Reproductions of Art Work, undated, (from Box 19, Folder 31) (Box 29)
  - Oversized Poster for Exhibition in Japan, undated, (from Box 12, Folder 6) (Box OV 31)
  - Oversized Poster for Exhibition, 1975, (from Box 12, Folder 21) (Box OV 31)
  - Oversized Poster for Michael Hall's Class at Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1973, (from Box 15, Folder 69) (Box OV 31)
- Photographs, 1876-1997, Series 8:; (Box 19-24, 29; 5.5 linear feet)
  Photographs are of Hemphill, family members, his residences, friends and colleagues including style editor Carrie Donovan, artist Rev. Howard Finster dancing at an exhibition opening, actress Alice Ghostley, Michael D. Hall, circus performers Vernon Goins and Tiny Hicks, Smithsonian curator Lynda Roscoe Hartigan, Neal A. Prince, and Jim Spies.
  Photographs of exhibitions include stereographic views of the International Exhibition in Philadelphia and the Exposition Universelle in Paris, and photographs of Hemphill's donation of his collection and its subsequent exhibition at the Smithsonian's American Art Museum.
  Travel photographs include views of South Dakota, Texas, the American West, Japan, Mexico, and The Netherlands.
  Photographs of art work sometimes include images of the artists with their work including Bruce Brice, Raymond Coins, John W. Fancher, Rev. Howard Finster, Theora Hamblett, Bessie Harvey, William Hawkins, James Harold Jennings, John Jordan, Charles Lisk, Alexander Maldonado, St. EOM, Fred Smith, Edgar Tolson, Hubert Walters, and Purvis Young. Photographs of unattributed art work arranged by the state in which it is located includes a Mardi Gras parade in Louisiana, a Mummer's parade in Pennsylvania, Lucy the Elephant-shaped building in New Jersey, and Holy Ghost Park in Wisconsin.
  - Photographs of Hemphill, 1930-1995, undated, (8 folders) (Box 19, Folder 55-62)
  - Photographs of Family Members, 1900-1980, (3 folders) (Box 19, Folder 63-65)
  - Slides of "Apartment and House," 1986 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Friends and Colleagues, 1920-1997, undated, (9 folders) (Box 19, Folder 67-75)
  - Photographs of Exhibition at Leon Loard Gallery in Montgomery, Alabama, undated (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Photographs of Exhibition at Heritage Plantation, undated (Box 19, Folder 77)
  - Slides of Exhibition "Joslyn Show," undated (Box 19, Folder 78)
  - Photographs of Exhibition Signs of a Living Folk Art at Museum of Early American Folk Arts, undated (Box 19, Folder 79)
  - Slides of Exhibition Carving For Commerce at Museum of American Folk Art, undated (Box 19, Folder 80)
  - Stereographs of International Exhibition in Philadelphia, 1876 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Photograph of Exposition Universelle in Paris, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Photograph of Exhibition Twentieth Century Folk Art at Museum of American Folk Art, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Slides of Exhibition "Cinci Show," 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Slides of an Exhibition in Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Slides of Exhibition Of the People, By the People, For the People, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Hemphill's Donation of Collection to Smithsonian and Subsequent Exhibition, 1986-1990, (5 folders) (Box 20, Folder 7-11)
  - Photograph of Exhibition Focus on the Collection: A Seventieth Anniversary Celebration at Akron Art Museum, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Exhibitions, 1968-1996, undated, (10 folders; oversized material housed in Box 29) (Box 20, Folder 13-22)
  - Slides of Travel to Africa, undated, (6 folders) (Box 20, Folder 23-28)
  - Photographs of Travel to Haiti, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Photographs of Travel to Holland, undated, (2 folders) (Box 20, Folder 30-31)
  - Slides of Travel to South Dakota, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Slides of Travel to Rocky Mountains, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Slides of Travel to Grand Canyon, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Travel to Texas, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Slides of Travel to Mexico, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Slides of Travel to Japan, 1976, (3 folders) (Box 20, Folder 37-39)
  - Slides of Travel to Old Canada Village, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Slides of Travel to Berlin, Germany, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Slides of Travel to Scotland, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Photographs of Travel to Miscellaneous Unidentified Locations, 1973-1978, undated, (6 folders) (Box 20, Folder 43-48)
  - Photographs of Artwork (Box 20)
    - Alexa; PoL; J. R. A., 1975-1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Blanch Ackens; Antonio Alberti, undated (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - James Anson, undated (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Felipe B. Archuleta, undated (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Larry Armistead; Eddie Arning, undated (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - N. B.; S. C. Baker, 1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - J. W. Banks, undated (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - James Bard, undated (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Rosa Brooks Beason; Solomon Bell; Louis Bertrand, 1976-1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Patsy Billups; Camille Blair, 1975-1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Jack Blumenthal; Alexander Borgardy; Rev. Mac Bogun, 1978, undated (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - John Knocton Bolyston; Mary Borkowski, 1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Mary Bradley; John Brewster, undated (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Bruce Brice, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Joan Bridges; Horace Broughton, Sr., 1985-1987, undated (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - J. Brown; Buzz Busby; David Butler, 1983, undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Elizabeth Capron; Miles Carpenter, 1971, undated (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Reginald Case; John R. Casmer; E. Casse; Anna Celletti, 1976-1983, undated (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - R. M. Chalmers; Thomas Chambers; Peter Charlie, undated (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - R. S. Cheek; Clark Coe; Raymond Coins, 1970, undated (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Jim Colclough, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Margaret Collings, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Cotrona; Ruth Reed Cummings, 1979, undated (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Spot Daniels; Henry Darger, undated (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - J. A. Davis; Minnie DesChamps, undated (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Numa Desroches; John "Uncle Jack" Dey; Thornton Dial, 1973-1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Samuel Perry Dinsmoor, 1971-1988 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Carl Dixon, undated (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Charles R. Dodge; Danny Dowler; P. S. Downes, 1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Doyle; John Drinker; John Durand, undated (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - William Edmondson; Minnie Evans, 1972, undated (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - John L. Fancher, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Ralph Fasanella, undated (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Albina Felski, 1972, undated (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Ferguson; Erastus Salisbury Field, 1975, undated (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Howard Finster, 1970-1983, undated, (3 folders) (Box 20, Folder 84-86)
    - Fortney Family (Doll Makers), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - George P. Fournier; Tim Fowler; J.O.J. Frost, 1975-1982, undated (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Harold Garrison; Victor Joseph Gatto, undated (Box 20, Folder 89)
    - Charles T. Gleason, 1974, undated (Box 20, Folder 90)
    - William O. Golding, 1972-1983 (Box 20, Folder 91)
    - Samuel Granatt; Rev. Dr. Graziani; Homer Green; Ralph Griffin, 1978, undated (Box 20, Folder 92)
    - Dilmus Hall; Theora Hamblett, 1965-1967, undated (Box 20, Folder 93)
    - J. Hamilton; Joseph Hardin, undated (Box 20, Folder 94)
    - Harkins; Alyne Harris; M. R. Harris, 1970, undated (Box 20, Folder 95)
    - P. Harrison; J. Hartman, 1970, undated (Box 20, Folder 96)
    - Bessie Harvey; H. C. Hawkins, undated (Box 20, Folder 97)
    - William Hawkins, undated (Box 20, Folder 98)
    - Richard Hayes; E. Hertig; Edward Hicks; Harley Hodges, 1970-1971, undated (Box 20, Folder 99)
    - C. Hofmann; John Henry Hopkins; M. W. Hopkins, undated (Box 20, Folder 100)
    - Jesse Howard; Sparrow Howlett; J. F. Huge; Ruth Hunt, 1971-1978, undated (Box 20, Folder 101)
    - Clementine Hunter; J. B. Huntington; Charles W. Hutson, undated (Box 20, Folder 102)
    - Antonio Jacobsen; Aronella James; J. H. James; James Harold Jennings, 1972-1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Rev. Anderson Johnson; R. Johnson, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Frank Jones; S. L. Jones; John Jordan, 1978-1983, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - John Kane; Phyllis Waxlander Kapp, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Allan Kaufman; Terence J. Kennedy; John P. Kirk; O. W. "Poppy" Kitchens, 1977-1989, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Gustav Klumpp, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Herb Kons; Sadie Kurtz, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - C. P. LaFrance, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Carl Landow; Thomas W. Lawson; Benny Layton, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - L. Lebduska, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Jim Lewis, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Harry Lieberman; Joe Light; George Arthur Lineback; Charles Lisk, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - William A. Lo; George Lopez, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Jose Dolores Lopez, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - George E. Lothrop; Adolf Lottokivich?; Max Low, 1995, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Annie Lucas; Charlie Lucas; Herbert Lyons, undated (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Joe M.; Louis Mader; Jacob Maentel, 1964, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Mahalchik, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Alexander Aramburo Maldonado, 1969-1986, (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 19-20)
    - Leuty McGuffey Manahan; George Washington Mark; Don Martin, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - E. L. Martinex; Justin McCarthy; Rev. Ollie McDade, 1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Gloria McDuffie; E. A. McKillop, 1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Arthur McTavish; Cora Meek; William H. Mersereau; Victor Millan, 1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Louise Millican; Peter Minchell; Charles Moore; Dealan Moore, 1968-1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Sister Gertrude Morgan, 1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Emma Lee Moss; F. L. Murphy; J. B. Murry, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Inez Nathaniel; Donnie Neas, 1977-1990 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - J. Niro, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Noah North, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Mattie Lou O'Kelley, 1977-1983 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Kevin Orth, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Angela Palladine; Charles Parsons; G. Patch; Glanman Paul, 1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Ellia Pawlovsky; Leslie Payne, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - John Perates, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Rev. B. F. Perkins, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Ammi Phillips; David Philpot; Piacenza; Pablo Picasso, 1971-1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Joseph Pickett; E. Pierce; Eunice Pinney; Horace Pippin, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - John Podhorsky; Polhamus; E. Polk; L. Pollard, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - D. C. Prince; Prior; Lamont "Old Ironsides" Pry, 1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Bamma Quates, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - D. V. Raffielle, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Martin Ramirez, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Raylib; Max Reyher, 1969, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Jessie Rhoads; Royal Robertson; J. Roeder, 1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Juanita Rogers; Michael Rogers, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Root; Elias W. Ru__, 1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Darlene W. Ruzotarski; Stephen Ryan, 1976-1980, undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - St. EOM (Eddie Owens Martin), 1975, (3 folders) (Box 21, Folder 49-51)
    - L. Sachs; Gladys Sanger, undated (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Jack Savitsky, 1978, undated (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Popsy Schaefer, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - J. H. Schenck; C. P. Scott; Jon Serl, 1982, undated (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - J. Seymour; Steve Shepard, 1985, undated (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - C. M. Sickner; Ellen Silverman; Elder Charles Simmons, 1982-1987, undated (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Louis Simon, 1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Pauline Simon; W. Sims, 1973-1978, undated (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - D. P. Skyllas; Dana Smith, undated (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Fred Smith, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 61-62)
    - Mary T. Smith; Simon Sparrow, undated (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Fannie Lou Spelce, 1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Henry Speller; Eliza Starr; Florine Stettheimer, undated (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - David Strickland; Clarence Stringfield, undated (Box 21, Folder 66)
    - Jimmie Lee Suddith; P. J. Sullivan, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
    - William Sullivan; F. H. Sweet, undated (Box 21, Folder 68)
    - Angelo Testa; P. Thomas; William Tinsley, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - Vena Tipton; Annie Tolliver, 1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - Mose Tolliver, 1985, undated (Box 21, Folder 71)
    - Edgar Tolson, 1968-1983, undated, (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 72-73)
    - Randy Toy; Toyzini; "Uncle" Howe Tuscon, undated (Box 21, Folder 74)
    - Clifford Vanover; Luis Vazquez; Vega; Verno, undated (Box 21, Folder 75)
    - J.B.W.; Alfred Walletto, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 76)
    - Hubert Walters; Henry Warren, undated (Box 21, Folder 77)
    - Joe Watbo; Weimer; Ira Weissman; Knox Wilkinson, 1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - B. Frances Williams, W. G. Williams; Clara McDonald Williamson; F. J. Winters, 1977, undated (Box 21, Folder 79)
    - Grant Wood; M. Wood; Dave Woods, 1969-1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 80)
    - Joseph E. Yoakum, 1983, undated (Box 21, Folder 81)
    - Purvis Young; Malcah Zeldis, 1993-1995, undated (Box 21, Folder 82)
    - Unidentified Artists, 1971, 1974, undated, (23 folders) (Box 21, Folder 83-105)
    - Unidentified Artists, 1975-1988, undated, (17 folders) (Box 22, Folder 1-17)
    - Art Work in Alabama (Alabama Architecture), undated (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Art Work in Alaska (Totem Poles), 1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Art Work in Arizona, 1975, undated, (2 folders) (Box 22, Folder 20-21)
    - Art Work in California, 1976-1980 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Art Work in Florida, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Art Work in Georgia, 1975-1976, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)